<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About me</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">Biography</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Hobbies</string>
    <string name="third_fragment_label">Contact</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="contact">Contacts</string>
    <string name="hobbies">Hobbies</string>

    <string name="Bio">
        "My name is Ketevan (Ketato) Abuladze, and I am from Georgia, a beautiful country
        in the Caucasus region. I am 21 years old, soon turning 22. I came to NYC to pursue my studies
        in computer science. My childhood dream was to become a professional tennis player, but unfortunately,
        due to health issues, I had to give up on that dream. However, I've found a new passion in computer
        science and aspire to be successful in this field. I have two brothers, one older and one younger.
        Interestingly, both the age gaps between me and my older brother and between me and my younger
        brother are 7 years. My family still resides in Georgia, and while I miss them dearly,
        I cherish the time we spend together during vacations."
    </string>
    <string name="Hobbies">
        "I have a variety of hobbies that keep me engaged and entertained. One of my passions is playing
        tennis, where I find joy and excitement in the fast-paced nature of the sport. Additionally,
        I enjoy the serene experience of riding horses, feeling the connection between myself and the
        magnificent animal beneath me. In quieter moments, you'll often find me engrossed in a good book,
        exploring new worlds and ideas through the pages. For a bit of excitement and competition,
        I also indulge in playing video games, where I can immerse myself in virtual adventures.
        Photography is another hobby close to my heart, especially film photography,
        where I relish the process of capturing moments on analog film and the anticipation of
        seeing the final images. And of course, I love spending time in the kitchen, experimenting
        with different ingredients and flavors to create delicious meals for myself and others.
        These hobbies bring balance and fulfillment to my life, offering both excitement and relaxation in equal measure."
    </string>
    <string name="email_address">"Email: Ketatoabuladze@gmail.com"</string>
    <string name="phone_number">"Phone Number: +1(929)264-2673"</string>
</resources>